		var questions = [
					{	question: "What is the answer to life, the universe and everything?",
						answers: ["42","fortytwo"]},
					{	question: "Belome and Toadstool are all names in what video game?",
						answers: ["mario","supermario","mariobrothers","supermariobrothers"]}	,						
					{	question: "Who wrote the song \"Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious\"?",
						answers: ["shermanbrothers","theshermanbrothers"]},
					{	question: "How many letters are in the word \"Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious\"?",
						answers: ["34","thirtyfour"]},						
					{	question: "What's the name of the wiki software Wikipedia is built on?",
						answers: ["mediawiki","mediawiki.org"]},
					{	question: "What color was mainly used on YouTube (besides white) on the 5th of may, 2005?",
						answers: ["blue","darkblue","aquamarine","greyblue"]},
					{	question: "Who was the boss on \"Who's the boss?\"",
						answers: ["tonymicelli","tony","angelabower","angela","samanthamicelli","samantha","mona","monarobinson","jonathanbower","jonathan"]},						
					{	question: "What is the name of the bit of software that will probably cause many applications to error on the 19th of January, 2038?",
						answers: ["unixtimestamp","timestamp","unixtime"]},
					{	question: "Now, how would you translate καλά from Greek to English?",
						answers: ["ok","okay","well","o.k","k"]},
					{	question: "What was Google's first stock price when it was just publicly offered?",
						answers: ["85","85$","85dollars","eightyfive","eightyfivedollars"]},								
					{	question: "What does the following Morse code: \".-. . ... .--. . -.-. -\" stand for in English?",
						answers: ["respect"]},			
					{	question: "What month was Google's website domain registered on back in 1997?",
						answers: ["september","9","09","sep"]},		
					{	question: "How do you write the following word: \"ɒbvɒnƚuɿɘ\" in non-mirror writing?",
						answers: ["advanture"]},
					{	question: "What letter appears on a registered trade mark symbol?",
						answers: ["r"]},						
					{	question: "How many words containing the letter \"V\" were said in V's opening monologue?",
						answers: ["57","fiftyseven","56","fiftysix","54","fiftyfour","53","fiftythree"]},
					{	question: "\"BackRub\" is known today as...",
						answers: ["google"]},
					{	question: "It's a city, university, and a dictionary. It's... ",
						answers: ["oxford","oxforduniversity"]}	,
					{	question: "What is the MPAA certificate number of the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?",
						answers: ["33087"]},
					{	question: "What is the fastest official record(as of 2014) for solution of a Rubik's Cube?",
						answers: ["5.55","fivepointfiftyfive"]},
					{	question: "What religious movement Buddhism emerged from?",
						answers: ["sramana"]},
					{	question: "What was the former domain of drive.google.com?",
						answers: ["docs.google.com"]},
					{	question: "What is the user ID (number, not username) of Mark Zuckerberg on Facebook?",
						answers: ["4","four"]},
					{	question: "What is the following MD5 hash: \"bd8e93043516f7ac296b4169981c0e31\" stands for in English?",
						answers: ["sha-2"]},
					{	question: "What was the name of a product Google launched and shutdown in 2012, that allowed you to create documents "+
					"and invite people to collaborate in real time by editing the content,commenting and even voting (simillar and prior to Google Docs)?",
						answers: ["wave","googlewave"]},
					{	question: "What is the first word appearing in the popup when trying to unrar a RAR file using the free version of the common WinRAR software?",
						answers: ["please"]},
					{	question: "The word \"asjdhksjdhfks\" is a word in which language?",
						answers: ["gibberish","gibrish","giberish","gobbledygook"]} 					
 						
						
						
						
						
					
					];